and how do they differ PMC Wagner
а чем они отличаются чвк Вагнер
is controlled by Russia And Gerkin And who
контролируется Россией А геркин И кто
else
ещё
there, no one told them anything, they themselves
там им никто ничего не говорил они сами
wanted and went Girkin just
захотели и пошли гиркин как раз
controlled it, he even
контролировал он же ещё даже потом
said later that they told me to leave, like
говорил да что мне сказали уехать типа
that means Russia controlled him Well,
то значит контролировала его Россия Ну
at first it didn’t control him then  they told me to
сначала не контролировала потом сказали
leave
уехать
about the third round
о третий раунд
that there is a new series being prepared Not me
что там новая серия готовится Не я
What Well, you haven’t posted it yet, you won’t
Что Ну пока не выкладывали не будете
post it I haven’t posted a lot
выкладывать Я очень много не выкладывал
from past streams because there’s not
из прошлых стримов потому что времени не
enough time to edit Well, after all,
хватает по монтировать Ну всё-таки
Post it not If you want, I can
Выложи не Если хотите хотите я могу
post it because you  something offended that
выложить потому что вы чтото обижали что
I posted the previous one shown
я Выложил предыдущую показано
want I can post anything you are kind of
хотите могу выложить ничего вы какой-то
sleepy today very sleepy very sleepy
сонный сегодня очень сонный очень сонный
Oh this is very imperceptible Well we just
О это очень незаметно Ну мы просто
Look I have a magic
Смотри у меня есть просто волшебное там
potion for awakening here look I take
Зелье для пробуждения вот смотри я беру
popcorn three pieces they say Eat
попкорн три штуки говорят Съешь
Magic
Волшебный
one
раз
two
два
three wash down with living water from
три запей живой водой
overseas it’s like they
заморской это там как
showed you today And now look around Donetsk
показывали А теперь смотри по донецку
Don superpower is awakening in me the
Дону во мне во мне просыпается
bruises under the eyes don’t go away
суперсила синяки под глазами не проходят
CPU
ЦП
vomer God how old are you everything about 41 years old
сошник Боже сколько вам лет всё о 41 год
Good afternoon I’m from Ukraine, the city of
Добрый день Я из Украины город
Khmelnitsk Where are you from And the bruises  they didn’t
Хмельницке Вы откуда А синяки так и не
get through, I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky in Ukraine,
прошли вот я из Украины город
you’re from
Хмельницкий Вы
where you ate
откуда съели
the bruises, you didn’t get through I’m from the city in Ukraine,
синяки не прошли Я из Украины город
probably Our video with you was edited,
наверное Наше видео с вами монтировали
yes, look, I’m Andrey from the city of
да да смотрите Я Андрей из города
Khmelnitsky with bruises under my eyes, where are you
Хмельницкий с синяками под глазами Вы
from? Yes, I understand, we already know each other  I
откуда Да я понял да мы же с вами
don’t remember Where did you
знакомы яже не запоминаю Откуда вы вы
hear
слышали
the news from Tell me from which city in
новость Скажите с какого города по
Donetsk
донецку
I heard that even in Belgorod you are
Это я слышал что на даже по Белгороду ти
in Moscow and he has figurines for everyone you know the
по по Моск и он статуэток на всех знаешь
figurines will never run out really
статуэтки не закончатся никогда правда
go to sleep go to sleep and so tell me
идите спать идите спать а так расскажи
what tell me what’s there
что расскажи что же там
and this  it’s good that it’s not Tell me that
а это хорошо что это не Расскажи что
there was
та был
an Arada, well, with a figurine
араду ну со статуэткой
in general, this is when he was without a weapon,
вообще это это когда он без оружия был
like
вроде
there were a lot of e-mo citizens Yes, a
там много было е смо граждан Да
citizen of Russia is yours Yes, do it against a
гражданка России ваша Да сделать против
citizen of Ukraine
гражданина Украины
Well, I won’t say because
Хорошо не буду говорить потому что этого
all this has not been proven, but at the moment  you are
всё не доказано но на данный момент вы
now laughing at the fact that the person,
сейчас смеётесь над тем что человека
look again Yes, I’m laughing, I’m laughing
при ещё раз смотри Да я смеюсь я смеюсь
because the person who Absolutely
с того что человека который Абсолютно
right, the person who
верно человек
suffered was innocent, there were no
пострадали невиновны там не было
innocents. Please tell me, did this person have a
невиновных А подскажите пожалуйста у
weapon on him or what,
этого был было оружие при себе или что
yes, look, this is a person who,
да смотри это человек который
uh, was a militant  Yes, look, he was a militant,
ээ был боевиком да смотри был боевиком
but wait, don’t interrupt the person
да подожди не перебивай во человек
who publicly said that we will rob everyone and
который публично говорил что мы всех и
everyone, he
всех ограбим говорил он
said, but look, Yes, when we
говорил а вот посмотрите Да когда
rob everyone, it turned out that it came to him And
всех ограбим оказалось ему прилетело А
what is it
что такое так
and what what Well, when a person
и и что что Ну когда вот человек так
says that, what’s wrong with him  we need to do Look,
говорит то что с ним надо делать Смотри
I’ll say this and if Putin Answer
я вот что скажу и если Путину Ответьте
my question When a person wants
на мой вопрос Когда человек
everything But what about a man
го всех вот надо всё А как же человек
without a weapon, he was just in the
без оружия он был просто в ресторане
Omni restaurant there was such a restaurant
Омни был такой ресторан
Sepa Absolutely right Yes,
Сепа Абсолютно верно Да
look, I’m very happy, I’m happy, look there was a
смотри радуюсь очень радую смотрите был
Separ restaurant in Donetsk  Do you remember this one,
ресторан сепар в Донецке Помните такой
you already know a little bit because of the old age, I
вы уже чуть-чуть знаете побо дре ста я ж
look at it, it works, look in
смотрите зли действует смотрите в
Donetsk, there was a separatist restaurant, a
Донецке был ресторан сепар в него
peaceful man came into it just to eat,
заходил мирный человек просто покушать
but there was such a Zakharchenko, don’t you remember such a
да такой был Захарченко не Помните такой
simple Alexander, Sasha Zakharchenko, with
Александр простой Саша Захарченко ещё с
the boys, just goes to a cafe? Yes, and
пацанами заходит просто в кафешку Да а
there  broads like that I’ll say more there was one
там бабах такой я больше скажу был один
such hero of Novorussia there this one was
такой герой новороссии там этот как он
Nokia his name was or what Ili sa and Mola
Nokia его звали или как Или са а Мола
Motoro he actually rode in the elevator like that in the
моторо он вообще в лифте ехал так в
elevator How can you take an action movie in the elevator
лифте Как можно взять и в лифте боевика
ah-ah-ah Maybe he’s unarmed there  I was in
ай-ай-ай Может он и безоружный там был в
the elevator, can you imagine, an unarmed
лифте представляешь едет безоружный
motor is riding in the elevator with flowers for his wife with a
моторо в лифте с цветами для жены с
cake And that’s it, of course a cruel
тортиком А тут и всё да конечно жестокий
person is very cruel I’m very
человек очень жестокий Я очень я
cruel I look Well, you know what
жесточайший я смотри Ну вот знаете чем
look again I don’t We are different
смотри ещё раз у меня не Мы отличаемся
from animals You tell me how you
от животных Вы расскажите чем вы
differ  from animals how do we
отличаетесь от животных чем Мы
differ from
отличаемся от
animals new still 41 years old Andrey I'm
животных новый всё-таки 41 год Андрей я
listening I'm listening listen
слушаю Я слушаю послушайте
listen Why is it needed
послушайте Для чего нужен
to take a
для того чтобы взять
person in order to slip him
человека для того чтобы подсунуть ему
a bomb So after all,
бомбу Так что всё-таки
how are we different from
ну чем Мы отличаемся от
animals And now listen to me son
животных А теперь послушай меня сынок
you came to our country of everyone I don’t
вы пришли в нашу страну всех Я никуда не
come anywhere here everyone here in a row and Tell me
приходи всех тут подряд и Рассказывайте
how this is possible
как это можно
and when are you here Luda By what
а вы когда тут Люде По какому
court what court are people here in Ukraine
суду какому суду людей тут в Украине
Answer I’m telling you what court you are in
Ответь я тебе говорю по какому суду ты в
Ukraine by Let’s bomb you Let’s
Украине Давай вас бомбит Давай
talk
говори
Arey watch Andrey
Арей смотрите Андрей
if on the territory of Ukraine there were some
если на территории Укра были какие-то
samples of someone
проб ктото
unarmed or something else, I am for
безоружных или что-то ещ Я за то чтобы
them to be punished, but they were punished in court,
их наказали но а наказали по суду то
that is, they found out what the problem was and
есть выясняли в чём проблема и
punished if they really
наказывали если они действительно этого
did this in the same way and
делали точно так же и
Ukraine generally attacked Ukraine they
Украин вообще напали на Украину они
went to court, look, there is a court, if
обращались в суд смотри есть суд он если
you have any complaints against Ukraine,
у вас какие-то претензии к Украине идёте
go contact him.
обращайте обращайтесь в он Ты
Look, understanding that you attacked Ukraine, you
смотри понимая что вы напали на Украину
are doing a huge
делаете огромнейшее
amount. Yes And you say, you know, it is necessary
количество Да И говорите Вы знаете надо
there according to the court. All of you attacked Ukraine. By what court did
там по суду Всё вы напали По какому суду
I  once again, under what court did you
Украину я ещё раз по какому суду ты
attack Ukraine? God, come on, tell me,
напал на Украину Боже Давай говори Вы
why
чего
Andrey, twice I was kind to you?
Андрей два раза я с тобой был добренький
Come on, third, under what court, you attacked
Давай третий по какому суду ты напал на
Ukraine, a girl under construction here, like, according to the
Украину строящийся тут девочку типа по
court, it should not be according to the court, come on, tell me, under
суду надо не по суду давай Говори по
what court, you attacked Ukraine  Why did
какому суду вы напали на Украину Почему
n't you Why did you make a deputy Why
вы нен Зачем сделали зам сде Почему
Why didn't you go to court but
Почему вы не в суд онов ский шли а
attacked Ukraine Why did you why did you
напали на Украину А почему Вы почему Вы
attack Ukraine when they squeezed Crimea out
напали на Украину когда отжали Крым ещё
again Why did you attack Ukraine I
раз Почему вы напали на Украину Я
say why Tell me you didn't go to the
говорю почему Скажи мне вы не пошли в
UN you didn't go  in it, the resolution is just
ООН не пошли в он резолюция как раз
Let's go look at the resolutions, it was yes, but it was
Пошли вон смотри резолюции он были да а
set on fire then look at the UN resolutions and
подгорел тогда посмотри резолюции ООН да
look at the resolutions of the Parliamentary
посмотри резолюции парламентской
Assembly of the Council of Europe Yes, where does it say
Ассамблеи совета Европы Да где Сказано
Yes, you are occupiers, you have to go It was
Да что вы оккупанты вы должны идти Было
like this It was Ukraine didn’t even attack the
такое Было Украина не нападала даже на
occupied Crimea, it didn’t attack, it really
оккупированный Крым не нападала правда
didn’t bomb  you had nothing to do with it,
не бомбило его ничего у вас не очем было
you, instead of going, even
вы вы да вместо того чтобы пойти Ещё ещё
now you’re starting to say it’s necessary in court, it’s
теперь начинаете говорить надо по суду
necessary in
надо по
court And you have a statute with your image,
суду А у тебя есть статут с твои
I say so, you have a
изображени я так говорю есть у тебя
statuette with your
статуэтка с твоим
image No, it’s a pity, let’s talk, you’re
изображения Нет жалко Давай гово Вы
very tired  you are very tired, you have
очень устали вы очень устали больше
nothing more to say, you told me the whole conversation
ничего сказать ты мне всю весь разговор
that I’m tired, I have bruises under my
сска что я устал У меня синяки под
eyes, yes, somehow you’re
глазами да вы как-то это как-то себя
behaving aggressively. Usually, this is what I
агрессивно ведёте Обычно вот что я
watched from you,
смотрел у вас
usually you’re you’re like that And you’re like
обычно вы вы вы такие А вы как А вы
What are you doing  Yes, look, you're already pulling it in. Well done,
чего Да смотри ты уже втягиваешь Молодец
you should, well, you knew that
вы это вы должны вот ну вы же знали что
you have today Stream is Thursday, Thursday is
у вас сегодня Стрим четверг же четверг
Tuesday. Well, it's still
вторник Так ведь ещё
Saturday. Look, instead of
субота Смотри ты ты мне вместо того
talking to me in detail, you're
чтобы говорить предметно ты
telling me. Go get some sleep, you didn't get enough sleep
рассказываешь Иди поспи ты не выспался
because I'm telling you the truth.  that you are
потому что я тебе говорю правду что ты
an occupier You came to this land to the
оккупант Ты пришёл на эту землю
People on your
Люде от твоего
behalf and you are also telling us
имени и ты е и ты ещ рассказываешь нам
You are also telling us
Ты ещё рассказываешь нам
wait you will support a special
подожди ты поддержишь специальную
military
военную
operation I will
операцию Я по пожи
tell you that you are against
с ты расска что ты против чтобы Люде
these guys killing the People
убивали эти ребята
Your guys are here for this  that
Ваши ребята находятся тут для того что
I think that they are there in order
Я думаю что они там находятся для того
to change a military operation
чтобы сменить военная операция
involves the murder of Liu
предполагает убийство лю
Vla a military operation to change power is not
Вла военная операция для смены власти не
for a change since it is military it
для смены раз она военная она
involves killing
предполагает убийство
people Yes, you can do the rest a
людей Да всё остальное ты можешь
diplomatic mission to change power
дипломатическая миссия для смены власти
negotiations this is possible a military operation and
переговоры это можно военная операция е
this is guidance  KATO
це наведение КАТО
in military methods, this means
во методами военными методами это значит
through the murder of key
через убийство ключевых представляете
people, that is, you look, wait, you are
людей то есть ты смотри Подожди ты
supporting now, you yourself understand
сейчас поддерживаешь ты сам понимаешь
that you support the killing of people in
что ты поддерживаешь убийство людей в
Ukraine and you start saying something, and what do
Украине и ты начинаешь говорить чтото а
I have to do with it? I’m just sitting on the
я тут причём Я просто сижу на
couch, you’re just talking a lot, you’re
диване вы просто очень много говорите вы
even insert a lot of questions into a word,
даже в слово вставить много вопросов
look at it there in Donetsk in the
вот смотрите вы там это на Донец на
Donetsk direction Luda and now both in
Донецком направлении Люде и сейчас и на
Belgorod and in Moscow Kaluga I and
белгородском и на Московском калужско я
so on, why are we in both the Donetsk and
проче с чего года мы вас и на Донецком и
Lugansk directions because where you
на Луганском направлении потому что где
howled more in Donetsk
выле больше в Донецке
No one only Russians  died No, not
Никто только россияне умирали Нет не
only look, that's when IT
только смотри вот когда ИТ
howls die and civilians
вой погибают и мирные жители
ye residents of Donetsk Correct Because
уе жители на Донецке Правильно Потому
you came with the war Yes Absolutely
что вы пришли с войной Да Абсолютно
correct And the war began just like now
верно И началась война также как сейчас
with now civilians are dying in Bakhmut,
с сейчас в бахмуте умирают мирные
civilians are dying, live in Bakhmut
жителите сес умирают мирные жите бахмуте
I'm asking you in Bakhmut  die mie
Я тебя спрашиваю в бахмуте умира мие
[music]
[музыка]
live those Because when there is a war Yes and the
жите те Потому что когда идт война Да и
troops converge those who are those who live in the
войска сходятся те кто те кто живут в
area of ​​the front line Yes the truth flies at them
районе линии фронта Да по ним прилетает
Why flies or not who
правда Почему прилетает или нет кто
started first Who was the first at whom
первый начал Кто первый по кому начала
you started to fly You started The first you started
прилетать вы начали Первый вы начали
to fire, look  we tell you everything
обстреливать смотри всё рассказываем ты
correctly, you said correctly who started first tell me
правильно сказал кто начал первым скажи
when the hostilities began in the
когда начались боевые действия в
Donetsk
Донецкой
region, exactly the date came, yes Who
области приехал именно число да Кто
arrived you arrived
приехал ты приехал
when the hostilities began in the
когда начались боевые действия в
Donetsk region, that’s it,
Донецкой области всё
come on, I don’t remember the date Well, there is the twelfth
давай не помню дату Ну там двенадцатая
Who is there On April 2nd of this year, you begin to
Кто там 2 се апреля года вы начинаете
say that the shooters  came in who is not
говорить что стрелков зашёл который не
considered
считается
a military man
военнослужащим
so PMC Wagner PMC Wagner is considered
так чвк Вагнер чвк Вагнер считается
a military man you are
военнослужащим вы
constantly I ask again PMC I don’t
постоянно Я те ещ раз спрашиваю чв гне
count the shooters not a
счита стрелков не
serviceman PMC Wagner the first
военнослужащий чвк Вагнер во первые
killed were from the Ukrainian side Yes you
убитые были с украинской стороны Да вы
killed them, look I’ll tell you
убивали их смотри я тебе расскажу
Deputy Gorlov Yes you are Russian militants
депутат Горлов Да вы российские боевики
Deputy Deputy  of the Gorlovka council Fisherman
депутат депутат горловского совета Рыбак
what are the
что
military Well, who is a fisherman fisherman a deputy of the
военных Ну кто такой рыбак рыбак депутат
Gorlovka council a resident of Gorlovka
горловского совета житель Горловки
and then look at this, take the walls of Chubenko
да потом это смотри возьми стен Чубенко
Yes, on Google there are militants like a
Да на Гугле пацана боевики ли типа
sixteen-year-old from Kramatorsk just
шестнадцатилетнего из Краматорска просто
for the blue-yellow
за сине-жёлтый
Girkin stop wait and which one Let
гиркин стоп подожди а какой Давай так я
me ask you PMC Wagner  Prigozhin is a
я тебя спрашиваю чвк Вагнер Пригожин он
military man Tell me Prigozhin is a military man
военный Скажи мне Пригожин он военный
or
или
not no, that is, I understand correctly
нет нет то есть како я правильно понимаю
that some Prigozhin is taking bakhmut
что какой-то Пригожин берёт бахмут
from you now, yes,
сейчас у вас да
I understand correctly that there were no
я правильно понимаю что там не было
military men there again, look, don’t relax,
военных ещё раз смотри не расслабляйтесь
then look, that means when I realized when the
отте смотри значит когда я понял когда
shooters Yes  he takes this, he’s not a military man, he’s
стрелков Да берёт это он не военный он
just some guy, and when
вообще просто какой-то мужик а когда
Prigozhin is this, this is the Russian army, he
Пригожин это вот это Российская армия
takes it, yes, the Russian Federation. Why did
берёт да Российская Федерация А почему
we catch you like that, we caught you, the beauty of the World Cup, you
так поймали мы тебя поймали краса ЧМ вы
caught me, look. What does this have to do with it?
меня поймали смотри Причём здесь давай
Prigogine is just
так Пригожин просто какой-то му
asking, you say  that there was a
спрашиваю вы говорите что там был была
Russian army there. Okay, look, so
армия России Хорошо смотри давай так
when there were armed people there, I’ll tell you.
когда там были вооружённые я вам скажу
Ko, when PMC Wagner, don’t wait, when PMC
Ко когда чвк Вагнер не подожди когда чвк
Wagner, now you’re constantly trying,
Вагнер сейча вы постоянно пытаетесь
look, I just turned down the sound for you so that
смотри я тебе сейчас скрутил звук чтобы
you don’t interrupt me, I’m asking you a
ты меня не перебил я тебе задаю
specific question, When is PMC Wagner
конкретный вопрос Когда чвк Вагнер
now?  is shooting at the Ukrainian troops, is
сейчас стреляет по украинским войскам
it the Russian military that is shooting or
это стреляет российские военные или
who? Come on,
кто Давай
tell me. Well, I’m also turning off the sound for you
говори Ну я вам тоже выключаю звук
Andrey turned it off so that you don’t interrupt
Андрей те выключал чтобы ты не перебивал
when I brew them. Come on. I’m
когда я те заваривать Давай Я те я тебе
asking you a specific question. Look, when the
задаю конкретный вопрос Смотри когда чвк
Wagner PMC is not here now. Are you pointing something out
Вагнер сейчас нет Вы что-то наводите ещё
again?  when PMC Wagner you run away You
раз когда чвк Вагнер ты ты убегаешь Ты
understand that Strelkov and Prigozhin are
понимаешь что стрелков и Пригожин они
simple people Yes, but for some reason
простые люди Да но почему-то у тебя
when in Bakhmut he is not simple, it’s the
когда в бахмуте он не простой это
Russian Federation that takes yes And when
Российская Федерация берёт да А когда
Strelkov it’s no, it’s just some
стрелков так это нет это же какой-то
Strelkov was Why is
просто стрелков был А почему
that so  come on,
так давай
speak when you want to say
говори когда вы хотите сказать
that
что
Andrei, well, you are ready to listen. You are
Андрей ну вы же готовы слушать Вы же
ready to answer,
готовы отвечать
speak up when a person comes to your territory in
говори когда к вам на территорию в
Donetsk and Lugansk, he
Донецк и Луганск приходит человек он
came there of his own free will or
пришёл по там собственному желанию или
something else
что-то ещё
started people,
начал людей
he became a military man or that his who
он что военным стал или что его кто-то
-hired even if he hired like this Show that
нанял даже если нанял так Покажите это
he is not a military man there was no
он не военный там не было
army, super I understand correctly what you
армии супер я правильно понимаю что вы
just said about Prigozhin, that is,
сейчас рассказали про пригожина то есть
some person who is not a military man
человек какой-то который не военный
came, wait, he came under the fire and started
пришёл подожди пришёл под бахмут и начал
people, I’m asking you what year who
людей я вас спрашиваю в чем году кто
was dying, look again, it’s not you who
умирал смотри ещё раз не это вы дальше
moved on No, you don’t answer the question, you
пошли Нет вы не отвечаете на вопрос вы
don’t answer the question in
не отвечаете на вопрос в четырнадцатом
1914, who started it, those Ukrainians started
году кто начал пер те украинцы начали
dying first, you started it, Ukrainians
первые умирать вы начали уть украинцы С
Which side did we start from? Yes, you started, Yes,
какой стороны мы начали Да вы начали Да
and look, No, which one?  then a citizen of
Во и смотри Нет какой-то гражданин
Russia is good. Let me
России хорошо Давай так я правильно
understand correctly that now a citizen is just
понимаю что сейчас гражданин просто
some citizen of Russia Prigozhin with
какой-то гражданин России Пригожин с
some
какими-то гражданами
former citizens of Russia who have been convicted, yes. Why are you
России судимыми бывшими да Почему вы
comparing
сравниваете сейчас
Prigozhin now with what happened in you? And how do
пригожина с с тем что было в ты А чем
they differ and that one is just a citizen of
они отличаются и тот просто гражданин
Russia?  just a citizen of Russia
России тот просто гражданин России
Russia hired Prigozhin where she hired
Россия наняла пригожина где она наняла
as she
как она
could Well they took it and hired it as they hired they took it
могла Ну взяли и наняла как наняла взяли
and allowed it And where is there some kind of document,
и разрешили А где есть какой-то документ
some kind of law according to which it is possible to
какой-то закон по которому можно Так
allow So No, well, I
разрешить Не а Ну я ещё раз
ask again in the fourteenth year when ra
спрашиваю в четырнадцатом году когда ра
where  Russia hired Prigozhin, look, you're
где Россия наняла пригожина смотри вы
leaving again, I understand correctly, look, you
опять уходите я правильно понимаю смотри
can say so Russia hired
так можно говорить ро Россия наняла
Girkin in the twelfth year, a
гиркина в двенадцатом году пришёл
man came, some uh, Russian,
человек пришёл какой-то э россиянин
you understand me correctly and started beating me
правильно понимаю вы меня и начал побить
up, you're here, I'm here, don't
бахмут вы тут я тут тут не
run away, look, it turns out that uh  I’m
убегай Да смотри нею получается что э
asking again, let’s make sure
какой-то ещё раз спрашиваю давай так
I understand the situation correctly. Let’s
чтобы я правильно понял ситуацию Давай
say, in 1914, some
так в четырнадцатом году какой-то
person, just a Russian citizen, came and
человек просто гражданин России пришёл и
started killing people here, not the Russian
начал тут убивать людей не Российская
army, but just some Russian citizen,
армия а просто какой-то гражданин России
so now in 22,
так сейчас в двадцать втором году
23, similar  the situation is
двадцать третьем аналогичная ситуация
just some guy from Russia came and
какой-то просто мужик из России пришёл и
started killing people under the bakhmut so these are
начал убивать людей под бахмутом так это
two identical situations
две одинаковые ситуации
Yes no And how do they differ
Да нет А чем они отличаются
in
тем
that the Wagner PMC is controlled by Russia And
что чвк Вагнер контролируется Россией А
Gerkin And who else
геркин И кто ещё
there no one told them anything, they themselves
там им никто ничего не говорил они сами
wanted and went RN as  since
захотели и пошли РН как раз
he was in control, he even later
контролировал он же ещё даже потом
said yes, that they told me to leave, like they
говорил да что мне сказали уехать типа
said he was forced to leave, and where to
говорили его же заставили уехать да куда
go back from the DPR to fold the post, they
уехать назад из ДНР сложить пост
put other
поставили потом других
people in place, which means controls
людей значит контроли
Well, at first I didn’t control, then
Ну сначала не контролировала потом
they said it
сказали уе
turns out, but how do you define
получается е а как ты определяешь
controls, no
контроли не
answer, no
отвеча не
Let's answer the year whether civilians from
ответим году гражданские со стороны
Kiev died or not, people from Kiev died Yes,
Киева умирали или нет уны Киева умирали
you killed civilians from
Да вы убивали гражданских со стороны
Kiev
Киева
and our Ukrainian citizens
да наших украинских граждан
were killed code Teri
убивали кода Тери
there you call a deputy of politicians Gorlovka
там депутат политиков называете Горловка
Rybak Yes local local deputy Yes
Рыбак Да местный местный депутат Да
guy Look here Take it Take it
парень Смотри вот Возьми Возьми на ле
now Civil please
сейчас Гражданский пожалуйста
Civil Chubenko take it
Гражданский Чубенко возьми
sixteen-year-old guy Chubenko
шестнадцатилетний парень Чубенко Вот
Take it now to the State Administration What happened they
возьми сейчас на ГУ Что случилось
shot him away, like in Donetsk he
расстреляли увезли типа в Донецке его
was seen by militants Girkin sy Yes with a
увидели боевики гиркин сы Да с
blue and yellow ribbon and he
сине-жёлтый ленточкой а он с футбольного
was on his way from a football match somewhere there to Kramatorsk So
матча где-то ехал там в Краматорск Вот и
they took him to the forest and shot him Well, that is, in
отвезли его лес застрелили Ну то есть в
1914  there, when they killed
четырнадцатом году там когда убивали
civilians, it’s normal And now,
гражданских это нормально А сейчас уже
when Wagner When Russia came in It’s already
когда Вагнер Когда Россия зашла Это уже
bad, it’s also not normal, our
плохо так тоже ненормально наших
civilians can’t be killed, you can’t kill them
гражданских нельзя убивать что вы их
either, it’s also not normal, it’s also not normal, damn it.
тоже ненормально тоже ненормально блин
We’ve been
представляете Мы же так Украина с
saying this since 1914. Yes, and he has a
четырнадцатого года говорит Да и он есть
resolution that you should take away  from there,
резолюция что вы должны забрать оттуда
look at yours like that Yes, they say a lot of things,
своих так смотри Да они много чего
they say everything, they say
говорят они всё говорят они говорят
In short, look
Короче смотри
Let's
Давай на
give it all to us,
бу отдай Нам всё
cynical adult,
взрослая циничная
like this, I'll tell you, an
вот так я тебе скажу
adult, support people in Ukraine, and you
взрос поддержишь людей в Украине да и
start
начинаешь
it, you start it, you start
это начинаешь это начинаешь это
justifying it, you burn Yes, Girkin is
оправдывать горишь Да гиркин - это
just what  - that's a man, but here's Wagner PMC
просто какой-то мужик а вот Вагнер чвк
This is no, this is already hired by Russia, yes,
Это нет это уже нанятый России да
handsome,
красавчик
look, I say, I think everyone saw it,
го вот смотри я говорю думаю все видели
how we
да как мы тебя
forced you in your own way, with your own face, and
поволи по твоему же твоим же лицом и ты
now you’re sitting like this. First of all, Andrey, you’re
сейчас сидишь такой Ты сначала Андрей ты
tired, you have bags under your eyes, huh?  now
устал у тебя мешки под глазами а сейчас
you’re sitting there
сидишь
like that and boring Yes, of
такой и скучный Да
course, let’s make excuses
конечно давай оправдывайся
What is a
Что такое
creation of superiority I’m happy for you But you have
утворени превосходства Я рад за ва Но вы
n’t become better because of this, you’ve remained the same as before,
лучше от этого не стали вы как были так
something struck you, you’re
вас что-то
enjoying the moment, I’m enjoying myself, I’m
пробило наслаждаетесь момент кайфую
just
просто
enjoying myself, let’s
кайфую давай
justify making excuses, that I should make
оправ оправдываться что мне
excuses, I’m doing something  did something bad so
оправдываться я что-то плохое сделал
that you support the murder of people in
чтобы нев ты подержишь убиство людей в
Ukraine,
Украине
I support my state that
я поддерживаю своё государство которое
kills people in Ukraine Yes, unfortunately,
убивает людей в Украине Да к сожалению
this is so, well, that is, you will support those, it’s a
это так ну то есть ты поддержишь те
pity you support
жалко ты поддерживаешь
I feel sorry for the people in
Жалко мне Жалко ещё также людей в
Donetsk in
Донецке в
Lugansk, so this is also
Луганске так это тоже
how Ukraine was occupied  Kherson
Украина была оккупированная как Херсон
was once yes it was once was
был когда-то да был когда-то был
once how things are in Bakhmut
когда-то как там в бахмуте
attention proly
дела внимание пролы раз
last
прошлый
time they said
раз говорили
that what Well, finally, here I was waiting for the
что что Ну наконец-то вот я ждал когда
word Bakhmut I tell me with Cherven how is
слово бахмут я говорю мне с Червень как
it Cherven in your opinion since June  months, your people
это Червень по-вашему с июня месяца ваши
are saying now Bakhmut Bakhmut Bakhmut
говорят сейчас бахмут бахмут бахмут
watch my videos about Bakhmut weeks
смотри у меня ролики про бахмут недели
ago 2 weeks ago 2 weeks ago you
назад 2 недели назад 2 недели назад вы
said that you will Free him Well, we’ll
говорили что вы Освободите его Ну
free him again Well, what’s the adj we’re
освободим ещё Ну и что в чём прил мы мы
in Bakhmut now, too, a hundred you didn’t take
в бахмуте сейчас тоже сто вы вы не взяли
Bakhmut even before  still, that is, and
бахмут ещё до сих пор во то есть и
look, Bakhmut is located
смотри бахмут находится от линии
12 km from the invasion line, you covered
вторжения 12 км вы за 13 месяцев прошли
some 12 km in 13 months. Let them stick in a little more. Let it
каких-то 12 км Пусть там ещё чуть
be 13-14, yes, that is, and you
всунуть Пусть 13-14 да то есть и вы
say. What’s there in Bakh? And what’s in Bakhmut?
говорите А что там в Бах А что в бахмуте
every month Damn I don’t know Go
вы мне каждый месяц Блин я не знаю Зайди
to my channel And take the word bakhmut there
на мой канал И возьми слово бахмут там
damn everyone in short damn tells me
блин каждый короче блин рассказывает мне
what’s in bakhmut what’s in bakhmut
что что там в бахмуте что там в бахмуте
and what’s in bakhmut
и что что там в бахмуте
And and and
Анд анд
go go
идите идите
to sleep There’s nothing to say So what’s there Bakhte
спать Нечего сказать Так что там Бахте
Tell me what  with you Tell me You
Расскажи мне что с вами Расскажи Ты же
said what was there in Bakhmut Tell me what to
сказал что там в бахмуте Расскажи что с
talk to you so in Bakhmut
вами разговаривать так что в бахмуте
Tell me in 1914 you were
Расскажи вы в четырнадцатом году
acquitted So in Bakhmut Tell me
оправдали Так что в бахмуте Раскажи
because there was
потому что там был
Girkin they were shooting because there would be a
гиркин стреляли потому что там бы
man from Russia Tell me about
человек с России Расскажи что всех
bombing everyone I listen  cut everything from the
бомбить я вы послушайте всё срезал с
bahnu Come on, let's talk about the four years, come
бахну Давай давай про четы год давай
on We We are coming back to the year
давай Мы Мы возвращаемся кчему году
you are constantly slating Let's go to the
которого вы слате постоянно Давай в
fourteenth year Let's get into the four
четырнадцатый год Давай залезли в четы
years, you say 54 people came in there and
год вы говорите там зашло 54 человека и
that's why the Ukrainian army had to
поэтому украинской армии пришлось
Shoot everyone No, I didn't say
Расстрелять всех Нет я такой не говорил
that, you'll come  no no no brother And now
это вы приду нене не браток А теперь
look, I’ll tell you how it was there, I’ll
смотри я тебе скажу как там было я тебе
tell you as if no, it doesn’t mean that Look,
скажу как бы нет не так значит Смотри не
54 people didn’t come in, that’s if we’re talking
зашло 54 человека это если мы говорим
only the first detachment of Girkin, 54 people,
только первый отряд гиркина 54 человека
and there the motoro climbed in and Babai and
а там же полез и моторо в и Бабаи и
all sorts of Cossacks were there  Yes,
всякое всякое казачество было да
for example, the city of Alchevsk, who controlled
например город Алчевск кто контролировал
some of your Cossacks, yes, they are also
какие-то ваши там казаки да типа тоже
just citizens of Russia and not military personnel And
просто граждане России да а не военные И
so on That’s the most impudent, impudent thing,
так дальше Вот и самое наглей наглей
your lie of the Russians that Ukraine killed
ваша ложь россиян ся что Украина убивала
civilians, civilians
мирных жителей мирных жителей это
you killed with your war Because when
убивали вы своей войной Потому что когда
it goes  the
идт
war flies in. Yes, some of it flies in and on the
война прилетает Да часть прилетает и по
peaceful side on both sides, this can’t always
мирным с обоих сторон это всегда не
be like this. Ask any
может такого быть Спроси у любого
military man when there are hostilities
военного когда идут боевые действия
until the civilians get a
до вот достаются ли мирным достаётся
certain percentage goes to the
определённый процент попадает и по
peaceful ones too. Yes, this is a war because of what it’s not
мирным Да это война из-за чего это не
because of that  that Ukraine is shooting at
из-за того что Украина стреляет по
civilians, or what do you think, for example,
мирным или вы как думаете сидит например
Poroshenko or Turchinov is sitting somewhere there? He
где-то там Порошенко или турчинов
says that nine-story building in Donetsk his
говорит ти девятиэтажки в Донецке ему
wife asked him to say. How do you
гово жена попросила Как ты себе это
imagine this? Do you think
представляешь А вы думаете у нас так
this is how it happens here? That’s the point, what do
происходит это вот в том-то и дело что
you think?  why is this happening with us? But for
вы думаете что у нас так происходит А
you, it’s not like that, you’re doing a good
вас те у вас не так вы делаете хорошее
job, and when Our troops
дело слу А когда Наши войска кого-то
kill someone, what do you turn off
убивают что вы отключа
when when I’m
когда когда я
talking before, what am I saying? that
разговариваю дово что я же говорю что
when yours accidentally there it’s a war, they
когда ваши случайно там это же война
kill everything else Yes,  there
убивают всё остальное Да в мире
is a war in the world And when a
происходит война И когда происходит
war happens, they die Unfortunately, civilians die,
война умирают К сожалению мирные жители
but there is a rule of war: don’t kill
но есть правило войны не убивать
the unarmed, don’t carry out terrorist attacks, and so on,
безоружных не делать теракты и так далее
don’t touch women and children and everything
не трогать женщин и детей и всё
else. And you sweep away
остальное А вы смете
the urat And I
урат А вам
told you bad words, laugh
сно вам сказал плохие слова посмейтесь
now, look, I answered now  I
теперь смотри ответил теперь я тебе
’ll answer you. You misunderstand that we
отвечу Ты неправильно понимаешь что мы
are talking about the Russians, we are not saying that you
говорим про русски мы не говорим что вы
shot there on purpose, we are saying that
специально там выстрелили мы говорим что
you started shooting at all, the problem is
вы вообще начали это стрелять проблема
not that you took and deliberately
же не в том что вы взяли и специально
hit the nine-story building. The problem is
ударили по девятиэтажке Проблема в том
that you came with the war and through this
что вы пришли с войной и через это
all the nine-story buildings are suffering. If you didn’t
страдают все девятиэтажки Если Вы не
come, look, it’s very simple, you
пришли смотри очень просто вы берёте из
take your troops from Ukraine and immediately
Украины забираете свои войска и сразу
stop shelling all nine
перестают как-то обстрелы всех девяти
floors somehow, it’s absolutely true.
этажек как-то абсолютно правда вот
Imagine if tomorrow Russian troops
Представь если завтра российские войска
and all these citizens with them are there
и все эти с ними там всякие граждане
for the territory of the Russian Federation.
пригожиным за территорию Российской
Ukraine Yes, there in the Russian
Украины Да туда в Российскую
Federation you think how
Федерацию ты думаешь как прекратятся же
the shelling will stop,
обстрелы
really and Or for example Zelensky will say
правда и Или например Зеленский скажет
Let’s Jah somewhere in the center of Donetsk
Давайте Джах где-то по центру Донецка
on purpose and they tell him there’s
специально а ему говорят так там же
no one there he says so let’s just Jah
никого нет говорит так давай просто Джах
And Yeah,
А Угу
well, they didn’t say Who  from the military
ну так и не не сказали Кто из военных
there was there there was a regular army of Russia
там был там была регулярная армия России
I tell you again Look or not I
я тебе ещё раз говорю Смотри или нет ещё
say again let there was a regular
раз говорю давай там была регулярная
army of Russia Yes there was a regular army of
армия России Да была регулярная армия
Russia you if you look Look you if you
России ты если посмотришь Смотри ты если
look let it be so you want I will give you a
посмотришь давай так хочешь я тебе дам
summary of the dead Russian military in the
сводку погибших российских военных на
Donbass  Yes, there is,
Донбассе Да есть
look, plus yours are already even saying that we
смотри плюс ваши уже даже говорят что мы
should not hide it already, and so everyone
уже должны не скрывать уже и так всем
understands that we were there and why
понятно да что мы там были и почему у
you have your officials and why you have
вас ваши чиновники и почему у вас есть
For example, he died in the Donbass in the fifteenth
Например погиб на Донбассе в пятнадцатом
year, for example, there is such a thing,
году например есть такое там военные
your military there are funerals  Yes, and in the units
ваши есть похоронки да и в частях висят
these hang and there are cemeteries with them, how they
эти и кладбища с ними есть как они
died then they took vacations and went on this Come on,
погибали тогда брали отпуски ездили это
let’s look Write to me, write to me
Давай давай смотри Напиши мне напиши мне
in a telegram and we’ll call you, let’s
в телеграме так и мы с тобой созвонимся
start, come on, I’m really already the second
начну давай вот я реально уже второй
time, you and I will do it, let’s do it that way
раз мы мы с тобой сделаем давай так
we will make a separate broadcast on
хочешь мы сделаем отдельный эфир по
your
вашим
military, on officers, on everyone, and so on, if
военным по офицерам по всем и так дальше
you want, with a separate subject, here I am,
хочешь сде отдельным предметом вот я те
yes, you can allow me to watch, I served in the
Вы да може разрешаю смотрите я служил в
fifteenth year, that’s when it
чем пятнадцатом году как раз это когда
all started And I’ll tell you how it
всё началось И расскажу как это
generally happened very
вообще было очень
often to us Well, it happens  such that the military
часто к нам Ну бывает такое что военные
goes into the
выходят в
city Well,
город Ну
let's go to the audience Yes to the audience And
давайте на аудиторию Да на аудитори А
when the popcorn runs out What would you
когда попкорн закончится Что будете
eat there were such situations when you
есть бы были такие ситуации когда ты
go out
выходишь
well bon
хорошо приятного вам
appétit there were such situations when you
аппетита были такие ситуации когда
go out into the city and to those I am
выходишь в город а к те меня
in a situation and to me the hem of the dude says
ситуа а ко мне подол чувачок и говорит
Listen, you’re a military man, let’s go there, you
Слушай а ты это военный идём там это
can earn money, he says
бабки можно заработать говорит в Луганск
you can shoot in Lugansk, you want to shoot there, my grandmother and I go
пострелять хочешь мы там с бабкой ходим
there, we have weapons, let’s go, and there were
у нас оружие есть пошли и таких людей
a lot of such people whose names were someone
было очень много которых звали кто-то
sog, luckily they
сог счасть
were released to the unit, no one went, wait,
отпускали в части никто не шёл подожди
look, you’re serving  in the part Yes, so you
вот смотри ты служишь в части Да так ты
went out for a walk around the city, a dude passes you. Let's
вышел погулять по городу тебе проходит
go there in Lugansk you can
чувачок Поехали там в Луганске можно
earn money and you say let's go and
заработать бабки и ты говоришь поехали и
leave and no one is looking for you in an hour and they are
уезжаешь и тебя в часе никто не
looking for you and and that is, it all turns out
ищет ищут и и что то есть это получается
like this. It turns out that the
все так Это что получается что
regular army went there  I
регулярная армия поехала туда я
understand correctly that all these people
правильно понимаю что все вот эти ваши
who fought in the Donbass are just
кто воевал на Донбассе это просто
some of the units
какие-то ли из частей
Yes, why from the units Well, you tell me
Да почему из частей Ну ты же мне ты сам
howl yourself, I’m telling you this, I was a soldier
вой бы я же говорю это я был солдатиком
Look, you yourself described the situation to me I
Смотри ты же мне сам описал ситуацию Я
didn’t go anywhere  I’m telling you, I didn’t
никуда не поехал Я же говорю я никуда не
go anywhere. And who could? There’s a military
поехал А кто мог Вот есть военный
contract, here’s a grandfather, here’s a grandfather. Which he
контракт вот дедок вот дедок Который мне
offered me, he’s not a military man. And he has
предлагал он же не военный А у него
some kind of weapon from Lugansk and he
какого-то есть оружие с Луганска и он
offers everyone to go with him without getting caught. I
предлагает всем не попадя поехать
think how are these guys  from Lugansk
об Я думаю как это пацаны с Луганска
they came to your region for [ __ ]
приезжали к вам в области по сру
nearby, I’ll tell you this,
неподалеку неподалеку я вам так скажу
firstly, they also went from Lugansk to Moscow.
во-первых ещё с Луганска в Москву ехали
It was a lot and there were
Это было очень много и по Ростовской
a lot of people in the Rostov region and there were
области очень много людей и слухов было
a lot of rumors. In short, look, I understood correctly
много Короче смотри я правильно понял
that the dudes who were leaving the unit
что чуваков которые выходили из части
take them for a walk Agirov go to Lugansk Yes
погулять их агирова ехать в Луганск Да
yes yes I can’t understand how a person who
да да я негу понять как человек который
left the unit for a walk should, for
вышел из части погулять он же должен
example, return to the unit by the evening so
например к вечеру вернуться в часть так
how can he go to Lugansk Yes, no
да как он может уехать в Луганск Да
one went, someone went, someone didn’t go,
никто не ехал кто-то ехал кто-то не ехал
well  like those who were traveling, how could they
ну как вот те кто ехал как они могли
go?
Поехать
Well, how do I know you say that like
Ну я откуда знаю вы так говорите как
Buto, I’ll
Буто я ж ещё раз
say it again, what will happen if a military man goes out for a
говорю будет если военный выт выйдет на
walk and doesn’t return in the evening at one o’clock,
прогулку и не вернётся вечером в час что
what will happen if they start looking for him?  every day, some
а что будет Если каждые 3 дня какой-то
military man leaves the unit and does not
военный уходит из части и не
return every 3 days Well, don’t you
возвращается ве каждые 3 дня Ну вам не
think that this is suspicious every 3
кажется что это подозрительно каждые 3
days Yes, it’s really interesting Listen,
дня Да действительно интересно Слушайте
this is a problem, but first of all, this didn’t happen,
это проблема но во-первых такого не было
listen Just wait,
слушайте Подождите вы самое
first of all, who told you that  someone
А во-первых кто вам сказал что кто-то
went secondly, they called mostly very
ходил во-вторых звали в основном очень
often from college and university And
часто с колледжа и с университета А уже
no longer from the unit Everything I understood, that is, the units
не с части Всё я понял то есть и части
too, it’s just that no one disappeared from us.
тоже просто у нас никто не пропадал Поня
You are
сначала спрашивал пацана Я понял что Вы
beautiful I understand that you want Oh you are
красивы понял что вы хотите чтобы Ой ты
running away okay Andrey All the best you
убегаешь ладно Андрей Всего доброго вы
never found any
там никогда не находили
military there the regular army
военных регулярная армия там никогда не
was never in the LPR
была в лнр
DPR and there were just people who
ДНР а там были просто люди которые
wanted to earn extra money and you started
захотели подзаработать и вы начали
screaming oh my God there the Russian army
кричать о боже там Российская армия
look they were just bombing cities  so these are
смотри просто бомбили города так Это
your problems, come on, come on,
ваши проблемы получается давай давай так
Russia didn’t send troops there, didn’t
Россия не направляла туда войска не
send troops there And you just fought
вводила туда войска А вы просто воевали
with some mercenaries from colleges.
с какими-то наёмниками из колледжей
In short, the boys from college come come
Короче пацаны с колледжа приходят
come see
приходят
You said there are
см Вы же сказали там
different guys there, you want to tell them for many
пацан разных вы хотите сказать им много
years, I understand correctly  in short,
лет я правильно понимаю что короче там
look, as I
смотри как я
understood, I understood from your story. So, a
понял я понял из твоей истории Так что
guy from Lugansk comes with a weapon,
вот чувак с Луганска приезжает с оружием
approaches the unit, once or twice he asks the boys,
подходит к части раз два просит пацанов
the boys don’t go, Because they need to
пацаны не едут Потому что им нужно
return to the unit in the evening, then he goes
вернуться вечером в часть тогда он идёт
to the college studio there and to the university, he says
в колледж там студи и в универ говорит
Guys, you guys, who are we IT guys, don’t want to
Пацаны вы на кого мы айтишники не хотите
go to Lugansk to raise money?
в Луганск съездить бабла поднять
IT guys are like that in nature, let’s
айтишники такие в натуре давай короче же
write this code now in short, in short, what are they
этот код писать сейчас короче мотн А что
paying, laugh, laugh
там платят ти го посмейтесь посмейтесь
Andrey, what does it look like dude, you
Андрей как это выглядит чувак тыж сам
laughed
заржал
damn yourself Okay, still in colleges, what are your
блин Ладно всё жи в колледжах какие
specialties?
специальности больше
they recruited more fabulous
набирали сказочный
just write in the comments yaks in
просто напишить в комментах яки в
colleges specialties the biggest Viva Buli
колледжах специаль найбильш Вива були
so for a trip to Lugansk for example there are
так для поездки в луганськ наприклад там
IT specialists there I don’t know I’m there
айтишники чи там я не знаю Ясь там
alarmists so what kind of specialties are they
будивельники так вот яких специальностей
recruiting the most there so that there’s a
так найбильше вот там набирают чтоб там
guy shooting from howitzers
с гаубиц пацан стреля
in short Oh damn I’m  I'm a bastard,
короче Ой блин я Я балдею
listen, so here's the butt Oh, cynical
слухай так вот це приклад Ох циничный
Russian people like that Yes, everything stinks, everything stinks,
российских таких Да вони все розу вони
everyone knows And then it begins Yes, the shooters are
все знають И тут начинается Да стрелков
just like a guy like that, having arrived Yes, but
просто короче який со дядька Приехав Да
Prigozhin doesn’t come, he’s like somewhere with
а Пригожин не прихожи он типа где-то с
him there Russia like he hired him there Chi
ним там Россия типа его наняла там Чи
damn
блин
Krasava Not  well, the finish line of course with
Красава Не ну финиш конечно с
with went out from the unit for a walk they say
с вышел с части погулять те говорят
Let’s go to this Lugansk And how did you get
Давай едь на этот Луганск А как тебя
happiness They
Счастья
let you go I realized that I said a lot
отпустили вин понял что богато наговорил
that at one time there was the FSB together so VN that details
что зараз там ФСБ вме так ВН та детали
rose and that Yak Tse bulo Yes it was taken in the
розу да тому Як Це було Да це бралось в
parts so Yak at once  You Wagner
частинах так само Як зараз ти Вагнер
allow them to stink
дозволяють им в вони
in prisons and so they came to the unit and
в тюрмах так и само приходили в части
said to Divi, in short, this is the contract and
казали Диви вот короче такой контракт и
so on and the stink came Yes,
так дальше и вони йшли Да
from the inlet of
с впуска вла
Vladakov, part of the inlet of the
дакова частинах впуска
pla And so on, they didn’t find a kid in the college of
пла И так дальше не пацана в коледже
an IT specialist, he was shot down from a beech tree, damn Boin
айтишника нашли он с бука блин Боин сбил
Yes
Да
just sign up for the channel to marvel
просто пишиться на канал дивиться
Like it, share our video with
Поставьте лайк поширте наш видоси тому
what we mi mushimo show to the whole world Yes,
що ми мусимо показувати всьому свету Да
it really stinks and Royan and Ukraine in our
що вони насправди и роян и Украин иншим
letter on y Ista I don’t know for you for you
пись на й Иста Я не знаю для тоб для тоб
there to marvel at the whole face Ale for you
там дивитись на оцей фейс Але для тебе
one two or three  clique Ale you trimae
це один два або три клика Але ты тримае
mene and I will be kasati va in me there Kupa
мене и я буду казати ва в мене там Купа
folov and in mene will be a classy mood to
фолов и в мене буде класний настрий щоб
robiti but cool video message on th Instagram
робити но крут вдео пись на й Instagram
bye Andriy
пок Андрий вот
like this, let me check with you
так давай я тебя чекаю